roojoom.com 2016-06-06

# Privacy Policy -

Roojoom (in this policy: “ **Us** “, “ **We** ” and “ **Our** “) respects your privacy. This policy explains the accepted privacy practices for our services through [www.roojoom.com](http://www.roojoom.com/) and through our mobile application (collectively – the “ **Service** “). It describes the ways your information is collected and used and the rights and options available to you with respect to such information. This policy is an integral part of the Service’s Terms of Use .

 **Information that We Process**

We process the following types of information:

(1) Device and traffic information – information identifying and relating to your computer and mobile device and communication and transmission data that your computer and mobile device generates when you use the Service;

(2) Personal details – Information that you provide Us when you register to the Service or when you communicate with Us or other users of the Service, including personal information that may be included in content you upload to the Service and any personal information that becomes available to Us when you register to the Service through a social network (in accordance with your privacy settings on any such social network).

The following sections of this policy provide additional details on each type of information that We collect and what We do with that information.

 **Device and Traffic Information**

We collect data related to your use of the Service, such as information about your location, the frequency of your use of the Service and content that you viewed when using the Service. We may collect communication and transmission data that your computer and mobile device generates or stores to help Us provide the Service. For example, We may collect and receive the operating system version and IP address you use once you register to the Service.

 **Personal Information that you Provide to Us**

Use of the Service and the creation of “webtracks” are available to registered users only. When you register to the Service (or while completing Our contact forms), We will ask you to provide Us with certain contact information such as your full name and an active e-mail address and to enter a username and password or provide other personal or contact details or attributes that define you as a user. We may collect additional information, as required, when We exchange communications with you.

We may also allow registration through various social networks account details (Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter or Google+). When registering through such networks, you are allowing Us access to your basic profile information. We can only access the information that the relevant social network makes available to Us, according to your privacy settings on the relevant network.

Please bear in mind that false, incorrect, or outdated, abusive or unlawful information may prevent you from registering and may impair our ability to provide you the full scope of the Service, or to contact you.

When you register with the Service, you may be required to provide a username and set a unique password that will identify you each time you enter the Service. We may require other or additional means or methods of identification, from time to time. You agree to maintain your username and password in absolute confidentiality and refrain from disclosing them to others. Make sure that you change your password frequently and at least once every six months.

 **Communications with other Users**

Bear in mind that when you upload your content to the Service, it may be displayed to other users of the Service. As soon as your content is displayed publicly, it will not be considered private or confidential and you should not have any expectation of privacy with respect to it.

PLEASE USE CAUTION AND COMMON SENSE WHEN YOU UPLOAD ANY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION. YOU ARE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY CONTENT THAT YOU UPLOAD.

 **The Ways We use your Personally Identifiable Information**

We may use personally identifiable information for the following purposes:

  * To provide and operate the Service – for example by:

(1) Displaying messages, notifications; and,

(2) Facilitating your communications and interactions with other users and with Us.

  * To send you notices and updates and to provide you with information related to the Service – through the Service interface or through e-mail, as available; We will not share your contact information or any other personally identifiable information with any third party, without your explicit consent.
  * To respond to messages that you send Us, and to allow Us to provide support and assistance.
  * To improve and customize your and other users’ experience with the Service.
  * To enhance existing features of the Service and to develop new features and services.
  * To prevent fraud, misappropriation, infringements, identity thefts and any other misuse of the Service.
  * To facilitate our internal managerial, archival, administrative and audit activities.
  * To contact you as and when We believe it to be necessary.
  * To comply with any applicable law and assist law enforcement agencies under any applicable law, when We have a good faith belief that our cooperation with the law enforcement agencies is legally mandated or meets the applicable legal standards.
  * To prevent imminent physical harm or damage to property.
  * To take any action in any case of dispute, or legal proceeding of any kind between you and Us, or between you and other users or third parties with respect to, or in relation with the Service.

 **Sharing Information with Others**

We do not share your personally identifiable information with anyone, and We do not sell, rent or lease your personally identifiable information to third parties, without your prior explicit and specific consent. We may share personally identifiable information with others in any of the following instances, or subject to your explicit consent:

  * To carry out the purposes for processing your personal information. For example, We may use affiliates, providers and business partners such as network operators, communications services providers and vendors to facilitate your use of the Service, to contact you and to send you messages.
  * If We organize the operation of the Service within a different framework, or through another legal structure or entity, or if We are acquired by, or merged with another entity, provided however, that those entities agree to be bound by the provisions of this policy, with respective changes taken into consideration.
  * We may share information with affiliated companies such as subsidiaries, sister-companies and parent companies to enhance our and our affiliates’ ability to provide and offer you a better service, as well as additional services that may interest you.

 **We use De-identified or Aggregated Information**

We may use de-identified, statistical or aggregated information, including information that We process according to this policy, to properly operate the Service, to develop and improve the quality and functionality of the Service, to enhance your experience, to create new services, including customized services, to change or cancel existing features and for other research, development and statistical purposes. We may share, publish, post, disseminate, transmit or otherwise communicate or make available such information to suppliers, business partners, sponsors, developers, affiliates and any other third party, at our sole discretion, provided however, that We will not knowingly, or intentionally share information that can be reasonably used to reveal your identity without your consent.

 **Access to your Personal Information**

You have a right to access your personally identifiable information if, and to the extent, We keep such data about you, and to update, rectify or remove such data. To apply for a copy of your information, please contact Us at: [info@roojoom.com](file:///C:/Users/Yael/AppData/Local/Temp/Temp1_documents-export-2013-10-02.zip/info@roojoom.com).

Before allowing you to exercise your right, We will need to verify your identity. We will make the information available to you, subject to any legitimate constraints and pursuant to the applicable law. We may refuse your request, for example, if We are unable to identify you, or if We believe that removal of certain information may jeopardize activities or features of the Service, harm other users, or compromise our legal rights.

We may provide you additional options to delete your personal information through the settings and preferences features of the Service. You may access your account and edit or amend the personal details that you provided during registration at any time, through your account settings. If you find that the information on your account is not accurate, complete or updated, then you may make all necessary changes to correct it.

 **Cookies**

We may use cookies on the Website. Cookies are packets of information sent by Our servers to your web browser and then sent back by the browser each time it accesses Our servers.

The cookies may contain a variety of information, such as the web pages you have accessed, session durations and IP addresses. We may also use cookies to save you the need to re-enter your account details each time you log-in to the Website or the Service.

We may use cookies for various purposes, such as to facilitate the use of the Service, to collect statistical information about the use of the Service, to verify information, to adjust the Service to your personal preferences and for information security purposes.

Some of the Cookies may expire when the session ends and you exit your browser. Other cookies are saved on your computer’s hard drive. If you wish to block Our cookies, you may do so by clicking the “options” button on your browser’s menu and follow the necessary instructions. You can read your browser’s Help file of for further information. However, bear in mind that disabling cookies may complicate or even prevent the use of the Services, or certain features thereof.

 **Securing your Personal Information**

We and third parties on our behalf implement security measures to secure the information We store and process. While such security measures reduce the risk of security breaches, they do not provide absolute security. Therefore, while We take reasonable measures to secure the information, We cannot guarantee that it will be immune from any wrongdoings, malfunctions, unlawful interceptions or unauthorized access.

 **Data Retention** ****

We retain different types of personally identifiable information for different periods, depending on the purposes for processing the information and our legitimate business purposes. When We no longer need to process the information that identifies you, We take measures to de-identify the information.

Generally, as long as you are a user of the Service, We do not delete information related to you, unless there are technical reasons that require Us to retain only portions of the data, or if We are required by law to delete it.

Please note that We will retain and disclose information when We deem it necessary to satisfy orders issued by courts and government authorities. We will notify you about the disclosure, only if We are explicitly permitted to do so. In any case, We may keep any aggregated or anonymous information for statistical, development, marketing and other purposes, indefinitely.

 **Important Notice About Children’s Privacy**

We do not allow children under the age of 13 to use the Service. If you are not yet 13 years of age, then you may not use the Service and must not provide any personal details to Us.

We do not intentionally collect personal information about children who are under 13 years of age. If We learn that a child under the age of 13 provided personally identifiable information to Us without verifiable parental consent, We will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete such information from our databases.

We strongly encourage parents to monitor their children’s use of online and mobile applications. We will delete a child’s personally identifiable information if a parent so requests by contacting us at [info@roojoom.com](file:///C:/Users/Yael/AppData/Local/Temp/Temp1_documents-export-2013-10-02.zip/info@roojoom.com).

 **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

From time to time, We may change and update the terms of this policy. Technical changes in the Service, new features and evolvement of relevant legal aspects, will require Us to adapt this policy.

We will notify you, either through the Service, or through any other means, in our discretion, of any substantial change that We make to this policy. The changes will apply to you seven (7) days following transmission of the display of the notice to you. You agree to be bound by all changes made in the terms of this policy. Continuing to use the Service after that date will indicate your acceptance to the amended policy. If you do not agree with any of the amended terms, you must avoid any further use of the Service.

We may also amend this policy to comply with any legal requirements. In these cases, the amendments will become effective as required or ordered and We will send you a notice of such change.

 **Contact Us**

We are doing our utmost to comply with this policy. If you have any questions, concerns or complaints regarding this policy, please refer them to: [into@roojoom.com](mailto:into@roojoom.com) . After receiving your request, We may contact you to better understand your concerns and will make all efforts to promptly answer your question, or resolve your complaint.
